Finding Aid for Perry Bullard papers, 1969-1992
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Perry Bullard papers
1969-1992
Bullard, Perry.
8587 Aa 2
The Perry Bullard Papers (1973-1992) document Bullard's service as a state representative from Michigan's 53rd district, primarily between the years of 1980 and 1992. The collection contains correspondence, newspaper clippings, committee reports and studies, bills, and briefing material on issues that came before the Michigan House of Representatives between 1973 and 1992.
67 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Perry Bullard (donor no. 6263 ) began donating his papers to the library in 1979. He and his staff have made periodic additions from that time until his retirement from office in 1993.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Perry Bullard was born September 2, 1942 in Cleveland, Ohio. He received a bachelor's degree from Harvard in 1964. From 1964 until 1968 he served in the United States Navy. Returning to civilian life, he entered the law school of the University of Michigan, from which he graduated in 1970. In 1971 he became the law clerk to Justice Paul Adams of the Michigan Supreme Court. In November 1972 he was elected to the Michigan House of Representatives. He won re-election in the 1974, 1976, 1978, 1980, 1982, 1984, 1986, 1988 and 1990 elections. In 1981, Bullard became Chairman of the House Judiciary Committee. While in the House, Bullard sponsored more than 100 bills that were enacted into law. Among them were the Open Meetings Act and the state Freedom of Information Act.
In 1992, Bullard decided not to seek reelection to the House and instead ran unsuccessfully for judge of the 15th District Court.
He died October 15, 1998.
The Perry Bullard papers document his twenty year career in the Michigan House of Representatives, especially as chairman of the House Judiciary Committee. The collection includes both Bullard files and files maintained by members of his staff. The files document the passage of acts (or failure of bills) through correspondence, staff memoranda, communications from constituents and lobbying groups, and all manner of background and printed material. The series in the collection are Correspondence; Legislative Files; House Judiciary Committee files; Topical Files; Political and Campaign materials; Publicity, Speeches, Clippings; and Personal Materials.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); Democratic Party (Mich.); Michigan. Legislature. House of Representatives.; Michigan--Politics and government--1971-1980.; Michigan--Politics and government--1981-1990.; Bullard, Perry.; Michigan--Politics and government--1951-
- Correspondence
  The Correspondence series covers the period of 1978 to 1990 (1987 letters are lacking). The correspondence is arranged by year and then alphabetically. The letters are from Bullard's constituents and cover a range of topics from personal individual concerns, politics, general legislative matters, and constituent opposition or support of specific pieces of legislation.
  - 1973-1977 (scattered), 5 folders (Box 1)
  - (miscellaneous), 1978 (Box 1)
  - [A-L], 1978 (Box 1)
  - [M-Z], 1978 (Box 2)
  - (miscellaneous), 1979 (Box 2)
  - [A-B], 1979 (Box 2)
  - [C-Mh], 1979 (Box 3)
  - [Mi-Z], 1979 (Box 4)
  - (miscellaneous), 1980 (Box 4)
  - [A-Be], 1980 (Box 4)
  - [Bf-Q], 1980 (Box 5)
  - [R-Z], 1980 (Box 6)
  - (miscellaneous), 1981 (Box 6)
  - [A-F], 1981 (Box 6)
  - [G-U], 1981 (Box 7)
  - [V-Z], 1981 (Box 8)
  - (miscellaneous), 1981 (Box 8)
  - [A-F], 1982 (Box 8)
  - [G-N], 1982 (Box 9)
  - [O-Z], 1982 (Box 10)
  - (miscellaneous), 1983 (Box 11)
  - [A-G], 1983 (Box 11)
  - [G-M], 1983 (Box 12)
  - [M-Z], 1983 (Box 13)
  - (miscellaneous), 1984 (Box 14)
  - [A-L], 1984 (Box 14)
  - [L-W], 1984 (Box 15)
  - (miscellaneous), 1985 (Box 16)
  - [A-L], 1985 (Box 16)
  - [M-Z], 1985 (Box 17)
  - (miscellaneous), 1986 (Box 17)
  - [A], 1986 (Box 17)
  - [B-Z], 1986 (Box 18)
  - (miscellaneous), 1987 (Box 19)
  - (miscellaneous), 1988 (Box 19)
  - [A-Z], 1988 (Box 19)
  - 1989 (Box 20)
  - 1990-1992 (scattered) (Box 21)
- Legislative Files
  The bulk of the collection consists of Legislative Files from the period when Bullard first entered the Legislature to the end of his last term in 1992. The files are of Bullard himself and some of his key staff, notably David Cahill, who was counsel to the chairman of the House Judiciary Committee, and Brad Geller, who was Bullard's personal aide.
  The files have been largely left in the order in which they were received. Thus there are materials relating to a specific legislative term and there are files related to topics about which there was considerable contention and which often carried over from one term to the next. These Legislative Files seemed to divide naturally into two subseries: Major Topics / Multiple Legislative Sessions and Miscellaneous legislation / Staff files.
  - Major Topics / Multiple Legislative Sessions
    "Major Topics / Multiple Legislative Sessions" consists of files pertaining to the major pieces of legislation supported by Bullard. These included legislation relating to the issues of plant relocation, the divestiture of state assets from companies doing business in South Africa or with its apartheid government, tort or liability reform, marijuana legalization, right-to-die legislation, among other topics.
    - "Red Squad" / police surveillance, 1977-1979 (Box 21)
      (repeal of the State Police Subversive Activities Act)
    - Various campaign reform and school finance reform bills, 1975-1982 (Box 21)
    - Uniform Marital Property Act, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
    - Legislative apportionment plans, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Insurance Redlining, 1976-1977 (Box 22)
    - Plant relocation legislation, 1978-1982 (Box 23)
    - South Africa Divestiture (public employees pension funds), 1976-1984 (Box 24)
    - South Africa Divestiture (public employees pension funds), 1976-1984 (Box 25)
      (continued)
    - South Africa Divestiture (public employees pension funds), 1976-1984 (Box 26)
    - Court-legal issues legislation, 1976-1985 (Box 27)
      (include bail reform, Friend of the Court and Family Court legislation, Court consolidation, etc.)
    - Voter registration reform, 1984-1986 (Box 27)
    - Unicameral Legislature proposal, 1981-1984 (Box 27)
    - Right-to-strike and labor relations, 1977-1980 (Box 28)
    - Freedom of Information, 1975-1979 (Box 28)
    - Tort Reform, 1983-1988 (Box 29)
      (includes liability of non-profit corporations legislation, medical malpractice, liability insurance, etc.)
    - Employee Right-to-Know (PA 397), 1979 (Box 30)
    - Statutory Will Act, 1985-1988 (Box 30)
    - Ticket Quotas, 1983-1987 (Box 30)
    - Drunk Driving legislation, 1982-1985 (Box 31)
    - Reauthorization of Office of Criminal Justice, 1982-1985 (Box 32)
    - Marijuana reform legislation, 1975-1979 (Box 32)
    - Medical malpractice, 1982-1988 (Box 33)
    - Firearms legislation, 1987-1992 (Box 34)
    - Bankruptcy legislation, 1981-1984 (Box 34)
    - Living Will/Right-to-Die legislation, 1986-1992 (Box 35)
    - Mandatory retirement of tenured faculty, 1985-1990 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous legislation / Staff files
    The second legislative subseries relates to more various pieces of legislation, largely coming out of the House Judiciary Committee. These files have been maintained by legislative session and House or Senate Bill number. Some of the legislative files, those maintained by either David Cahill or Brad Geller, are arranged by date. These files are valuable in their documentation of the progress of a piece of legislation through the Legislature and the full House. Included are copies of the bill, drafts and other modifications, and memoranda to Bullard from staff discussing or offering criticism of a bill. The files also contain background information about the topic covered by the legislation.
    - 1973-1976, primarily 1974-1975
      - House Bill number (Box 36)
        - HB203 and 205: Impeachment of Richard Nixon, 1973-1974 (Box 36)
        - HB4020 Anti-littering laws, 1973 (Box 36)
        - HB4142 Unemployment benefits to include medical insurance coverage, 1975 (Box 36)
        - HB4513 Regulating advertising of gasoline stations, 1974-1975 (Box 36)
        - HB4982 Bicycles, 1975 (Box 36)
        - HB4990 Regulation of Farmer-employee relations, 1975 (Box 36)
        - HB5052 Rights of prisoners, 1973 (Box 36)
        - HB5178 Labeling of perishable foods, 1973-1975 (Box 36)
        - HB5506 Traffic laws re. Hitch-hiking, 1973-1974 (Box 36)
        - HB5689 Licensing of Health Care Facilities, 1973 (Box 36)
        - HB5740 Voter registration, 1974 (Box 36)
        - HB5930 Public Service Commission empowered to regulate utilities' wages and salaries, 1974 (Box 36)
        - HB5992 Benefits for veterans, 1974 (Box 36)
        - HB6205 Escaped prisoners, 1974 (Box 36)
      - Legislative Service Bureau number
        - LSB2530 Recreation Trails, 1973-1975 (Box 36)
        - LSB6135 Exemption from property tax for private forest reserves, 1976 (Box 36)
        - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - 1977-1978
      - Legislative Service Bureau number
        - 362: Required automatic damper on furnaces, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1075 Allocate a percentage of state contracts to minority businesses, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1081 Create residential utility consumer action group, 1975-1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1222 State repurchase of Pigeon River Forest oil leases, 1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1233 Community Colleges communications instruction, 1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1237 Consumer Protection (Box 36)
        - LSB1243 Labeling of products, 1973-1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1246 Income Tax deduction for employment related expense, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1248 Prohibit discrimination in insurance policies, 1975-1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1257 Allow students at state financed schools to live off campus, 1973-1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1266 Permit establishment of Women's Commissions at county level, 1973-1975 (Box 36)
        - LSB1267 Certification of nursing homes, homes for aged, etc., 1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1268 Require expenditure of funds for art in state buildings, 1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1277 Revise requirements for jury service, selection, etc. (Box 36)
        - LSB1280a: Criminal records procedure, 1973-1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1285 Sexual assault by spouse, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1286 Indigents' right to choose counsel, 1973-1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1305 School District reorganization, 1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1315 Tenant-Landlord relations, 1975-1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB1319 Patient's Rights in health care facilities, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB1521 Interest charges by banks, 1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB2205 Prohibit discrimination in housing against recipients of public assistance, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB2521 Wiretapping, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB3275 Barrier Free design board meetings, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB3948 Pollution monitoring by state, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB4393 Income Tax credit for alternate power source installation, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB4690 Permit advertising by optometrists, 1975-1976 (Box 36)
        - LSB4867 Permit tax deferrals, 1977 (Box 36)
        - LSB5232 Prevent cruelty to animals at rodeos, etc., 1977 (Box 36)
        - Bill drafting requests (Box 36)
    - David Cahill (counsel to the House Judiciary Committee)
      - 1979-1988 (Box 37)
      - (includes some earlier material; major topics include Ann Arbor Nuclear Free Zone resolution and victim rights legislation), 1985-1986 (Box 37)
      - (include some material relating to "chop shop" legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 38)
      - (fragmentary), 1987-1988 (Box 39)
      - (arranged by bill no.). Major topics include "heinous crime" legislation, 1989-1990 (Box 39)
      - (arranged by bill no.), 1989-1990 (Box 40)
      - 1985-1989 (mainly Anti-Crime Program, 1987-1988 and related legislation) (Box 41)
      - 1985-1989 (mainly Anti-Crime Program, 1987-1988 and related legislation) (Box 42)
    - Brad Geller (Aide to Perry Bullard) (Box 43)
      - (miscellaneous legislation), 1987-1990 (Box 43)
    - Various legislation and staff, 1970s-1980s (Box 44)
      (unprocessed)
    - Various legislation and staff, 1970s-1980s (Box 45)
- House Judiciary Committee files
  Associated with these files is a small series of House Judiciary Committee files. These consist of agenda of the meeting of the committee and a scattering of materials from the various subcommittees.
  - Agenda of Meetings, 1975-1988 (Box 46)
  - Subcommittees files, 1975-1988 (Box 46)
- Topical files
  An important, but somewhat disparate series, is the Topical Files. Over the course of his career, Perry Bullard and his staff made more than forty separate accessions of materials to the library. These came to the library as material was no longer needed or as file space was required. The most convenient way to deal with this material was to create subject files, largely by chronological blocks of time, but with much overlap. There are currently four separate topical files with information on all public policy issues, citizen concerns, and specific pieces of legislation. These sets of Topical Files should be used with the Legislative Files for material on South Africa Divestiture among other topics.
  - 1973-1986
    - Animal cruelty, 1977-1978 (Box 47)
    - Anti-trust Resolution and related, 1983-1984 (Box 47)
    - Arms control, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Artists, 1980-1982 (Box 47)
    - Automobile Accident Confidentiality, 1978-1981 (Box 47)
    - Automobile Lemon Bill, 1977-1982 (Box 47)
    - Balanced budget amendment, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Beer and Wine Tax Refund, 1980-1984 (Box 47)
    - Bicycling, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Canada (public policy issues), 1977-1978 (Box 47)
    - Capital Punishment, 1973; 1977 (Box 47)
    - Civil Rights Committee, 1976; 1978 (Box 47)
    - Client/Counselor Confidentiality, 1983-1985 (Box 47)
    - Cobblestone Farm Association, 1976-1978 (Box 47)
    - Constitutional Convention (proposed right-to-life amendment), 1977 (Box 47)
    - Co-op Preschool Tax Exemption, 1982-1985 (Box 47)
    - Courts, 1973-1985 (Box 47)
    - Criminal Record Expungement, 1982-1985 (Box 47)
    - Employee Legislation
      - Employee Ownership
        - Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 47)
        - General, 1977-1980 (Box 47)
      - Employee Right-to-Know
        - Correspondence, 1977-June 1978 (Box 47)
        - Correspondence, July 1978-1983 (Box 47)
        - General, 1977-1978 (Box 47)
      - Political Rights of Public Employees, 1979 (Box 47)
      - Whistleblowers' Protection, 1979-1982 (Box 47)
    - Employee Retirement Security Act, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Energy Conservation
      - Alternative Sources, 1975-1981 (Box 47)
      - Financing, 1979-1981 (Box 47)
    - Fair Trade Law Repeal, 1975 (Box 47)
    - Family Court bills, 1975-1977 (Box 47)
    - Firearms, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Fluoridation, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Foster care, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Fuel and Vehicle Taxation, 1976-1977 (Box 47)
    - Fuel Tax Refund, Community Action Agencies, 1979-1980 (Box 47)
    - General Motors, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Geralds, (Rep. Monte) hearings, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Hunting and Fishing Pleas, 1981-1984 (Box 47)
    - Huron Portage Yacht Club, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Insurance (HB5196/6322) (Box 47)
    - Iron Ore Severance Tax, 1975-1978 (Box 47)
    - Jackson Community College/Prison Employees, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Kensington Park, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Landlord-Tenant Bills
      - General, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
      - General, 1977-1979 (Box 48)
      - Support Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 48)
    - Library Privacy Act, 1979-1986 (Box 48)
    - Mechanic Certification, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Medical Malpractice (Support materials only), 1985 (Box 48)
    - Michigan Occupational Safety and Health Act Revisions
      - Correspondence and Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 48)
      - General, 1979-1982 (Box 48)
      - Report, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Michigan Office of Criminal Justice Programs (Box 48)
    - Midwifery, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Migrant Labor housing, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Milk, Regulation on Sale, 1974-1977 (Box 48)
    - Non-Smokers Rights, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
    - Nursing homes, 1973-1978 (Box 48)
    - Nursery (child care centers), Fire Inspections, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Obscenity, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
    - Oil and Gas Severance Tax, 1976-1983 (Box 48)
    - Pigeon River, 1976-1977 (Box 48)
    - Pirgim Fee, 1975-1977 (Box 48)
    - Recounts, U.S. Congress, 1975-1977 (Box 48)
    - Restaurants (non-smoking areas and liquor licenses), 1978 (Box 48)
    - Reserve Police Officers Training
      - General, 1978-1980 (Box 48)
      - Survey Results, 1979 (Box 48)
    - School Property Sale, 1978-1979 (Box 48)
    - Seat Belt and Helmet Regulations, 1982-1983 (Box 48)
    - Single business tax, 1975-1978; 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Stevens, J.P., Boycott
      - General, 1979-1980 (Box 48)
      - Departmental Purchases, Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 48)
    - Student Loans
      - Assistance, 1975-1981 (Box 48)
      - Disclosure, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
    - Students' Right to Sit on Governing Boards, 1973-1976 (Box 48)
    - Tax Anticipation Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 48)
    - Voting Powers of Township Officials, 1981 (Box 48)
    - Welfare Shelter Payments, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 1974-1989
    - Airborne Warning and Communication System resolution and MX missile, 1983-1985 (Box 49)
    - Ann Arbor State Street Area Association, 1986-1987 (Box 49)
    - Attorney General (Office) Opinions and other Communications (Box 49)
    - Balanced Budget Amendment and related (Box 49)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield rate increases, 1978-1980 (Box 49)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield, mutualization of, 1985-1988 (Box 49)
    - Bottle Bill, 1979 (Box 49)
    - Caucus Anti-Crime Program, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Central America (Nicaragua political and military situation), 1980s; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Congratulatory letters from political campaigns, 1970s (Box 49)
    - Cooperatives, 1979 (Box 49)
    - Corporate "propaganda" in schools (Box 49)
    - Council of State Manufacturing Associations (Box 49)
    - Covenant Not to Compete legislation, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Crime (Clack) Summit, 1989 (Box 49)
    - DES (diethylstilbestrol) awareness, 1985 (Box 49)
    - District Court, 14th, 1984; 6 folders (Box 49)
    - Divorce, 1970s; 1980s (Box 49)
    - DNA research bill, 1977-1979 (Box 49)
    - Domestic Violence, 1979-1984 (Box 49)
    - Dread disease insurance policies legislation, 1990 (Box 49)
    - Drinking Age, 1976-1979 (Box 49)
    - Drug legislation, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Education, various legislation (Box 49)
    - Environmental concerns, 1978-1983 (Box 49)
    - Ethnic intimidation, 1987 (Box 49)
    - European Community visit, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Flex-Time, 1980 (Box 50)
    - Great Lakes environmental research, 1982; 1985 (Box 50)
    - Grenada invasion, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Guardianship legislation, 1985-1989 (Box 50)
    - Handicap discrimination, 1987-1988 (Box 50)
    - Heartline Program, 1985 (Box 50)
    - High Speed police chases, legislation regarding, 1983-1987 (Box 50)
    - Individual Retirement Account legislation (Box 50)
    - Insurance premium cycles, 1986 (Box 50)
    - Jobs With Peace resolution, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Judgeship retirement system, 1984-1985 (Box 50)
    - Juvenile Code, correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 50)
    - Juvenile Justice Reforms
      - Child Support, 1985-1986 (Box 50)
      - Treatment of Juveniles, 1985-1987 (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-1987 (Box 50)
    - Juvenile Waiver, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Labor (State House Labor Committee), 1977-1979 (Box 50)
    - Libraries, legislation regarding, 1980-1981 (Box 50)
    - Licensing Boards, 1974-1978 (Box 50)
    - Market Opinion Research Proposal, 1980 (Box 50)
    - Martial Arts Weapons legislation, 1985 (Box 50)
    - Medical records, confidentiality of, 1986-1988 (Box 50)
    - Medicare Fair Billing and Reimbursement Act (Box 50)
    - Michigan Council for the Arts, 1974-1976 (Box 50)
    - Michigan Judges Association conferences, 1983; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Michigan State Police
      - General, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Use of tax information, 1986 (Box 50)
    - Nestle Company boycott, 1979 (Box 50)
    - Nuclear Plants, 1980s (Box 50)
    - Nurse anesthetists, 1986-1989 (Box 50)
    - Prisons, 1973-1978 (Box 50)
    - Probate Code, 1978-1985 (Box 50)
    - Reasonable charges, medical (Box 50)
    - Red Squad files, 1980-1983 (Box 50)
    - Seafarer Project, 1976 (Box 50)
    - Schembechler (Bo) incident, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Sex discrimination issues (Title IX and comparable worth), 8 folders (Box 51)
    - Sexual orientation legislation (Box 51)
    - Solar Access (Box 51)
    - Solar Tax Credits (Box 51)
    - Taxation miscellaneous (Box 51)
    - Tax Support for Public Broadcasting (Box 51)
    - Teacher's retirement, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
    - Telephone monitoring, 1976-1977 (Box 51)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, payout report and evaluation, 1985-1986 (Box 51)
    - "Truth-in-Heating, 1982 (Box 51)
    - Tuition voucher, 1978 (Box 51)
    - Unemployment (general), 1980 (Box 51)
    - University of Michigan Student Code, 1984-1985 (Box 51)
    - Welfare (Michigan), 1980-1982 (Box 51)
    - Williams International civil disobedience, 1985 (Box 51)
    - Wine Auctions at Charitable Events, 1984 (Box 51)
    - Workmen's Compensation legislation (Box 51)
    - Youth unemployment, 1976 (Box 51)
  - 1973-1990
    - Ann Arbor Tree Cutting Incident, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Article VI Judiciary Branch Revision, 1989 (Box 52)
    - Bullard Bills and Resolutions, 1973-1986 (Box 52)
    - Campus Police Powers (HB5165), 1990 (Box 52)
    - Cap-Stun (HB5475, 5476), 1990 (Box 52)
    - Chattel Mortgage (HB4980), 1985 (Box 52)
    - Chemical Substances "Right to Know" (HB5357), 1984 (Box 52)
    - Consumer Cooperatives (HB4335), 1983-1984 (Box 52)
    - CPR Training in High Schools (HB5379), 1986 (Box 52)
    - CPR Training in High Schools (HB5379), 1987 (Box 52)
    - CPR Training in High Schools, Bills from Previous Sessions, 1977-1979 (Box 52)
    - CPR Training in High Schools, Press Clippings, 1977-1986 (Box 52)
    - CPR Training in High Schools, Support Letters, 1978-1986 (Box 52)
    - Crime Package, 1987 (Box 52)
    - Death Penalty for Snipers (HB4011), 1989 (Box 52)
    - Degradable Plastic Bags, 1989 (Box 52)
    - Dog and Cock Fighting (HB4909, HB5595), 1988-1989 (Box 52)
    - Emancipation of Minors (HB5253, HB5254), 1987 (Box 52)
    - Endangered Species, 1976 (Box 52)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Air Quality Inspection and Maintenance Program, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Environmental Protection on Water Contamination, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Fifth Judicial Circuit Division (HB4636), 1989 (Box 52)
    - Filing Fee Increases (HB4088), 1989 (Box 52)
    - Fine Art (HB5274 HB5275), 1981 (Box 52)
    - Fine Art Multiples (HB4300 HB4301, HB4302, HB4303), 1983 (Box 52)
    - Fine Art Multiples (HB4070, HB4071, HB4072), 1985 (Box 52)
    - Fine Art Multiples (HB4066, HB4067, HB4068, SB55, SB56), 1987 (Box 52)
    - Frithjof "Future of Work", 1983 (Box 52)
    - Gay Rights
      - Bullard Speech, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 52)
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Decriminalization of Adult Consensual Sexual Behavior (HB5624), 1976-1984 (Box 52)
      - Elliot Larsen Civil Rights Act, 1983-1987 (Box 52)
      - Legal Concerns (HB5000), 1983 (Box 52)
      - Michigan Organization for Human Rights, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Other States, 1981-1983 (Box 52)
      - Publications, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Support Letters, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 52)